Hi everyone
I'm Eagle
Welcome to EVOX SoundAI
AI Digital Human Workstation
This software has many unique features
For example, the operation method of multiple AI voice roles speaking simultaneously in AI dubbing
more convenient sound effect insertion
ultimate layered output
In terms of AI lip-syncing
The software supports multi-character selection to assign voices.
Here it is divided into two video segments in total, supporting head tilting, subtitle matching, and preservation of ambient sounds.
Subtitle matching with ambient sound retention
I’ve seen pictures. It’s full of history. Let's first listen to
What kind of effect can this dubbing software achieve?
The young hero knelt before the Buddha in the ancient temple
In this silent late night
He heard two voices from the depths of his soul
Give up. Do you really think you can save the world?
Turn back before it's too late
Put down your sword
You can live a peaceful and stable life.
Isn't this what you've always wanted?
Don't listen to him
Pick up the sword
Just kill them all
All the power and wealth in this world will be yours.
Those are all illusions
Only power is eternal. Take action now.
Take no action
Tell me what your choice really is, what is it
Well, this feels pretty good
Right then, let me quickly demonstrate this process first
and then explain in detail
We can use AI tools to generate this text.
There are currently 4 columns
They correspond to the text, sentences, and audio output respectively.
You can temporarily disable some columns
Clear the sentences first
The text enclosed in curly braces is the character's name
If the character name is followed by 'left' or 'right'
it means that these two characters are speaking different lines simultaneously
if there is a plus sign between character names
represents speaking the same lines simultaneously
Click on multi-character settings for multi-character recognition
Three roles have now been identified
Bind each of these three roles to an audio. First, the narrator, the prince's current choice of this audio.
Select this audio and click
Xiao Wang
Your item, we use Master Kumarajiva
Xiao Zhang, I'll use this great monk
After selecting, click 'Add to Sentence'
We can see that as long as they are speaking simultaneously
On the left side, there is a color like this
indicates that it belongs to a group
Then turn off the text column
You can select any line
take a look
Click to preview the young hero
kneeling before the Buddha in the ancient temple
In this silent late night
heard two voices from the depths of the soul
Chief Tao's voice indeed lives up to what Prime Minister Lü had anticipated
If you think this voice doesn't suit us
Change to another voice
Click to lose the tone
Press the scroll wheel
Use the scroll wheel here to turn the volume down a bit
Select composition
The young hero kneels before the Buddha in the ancient temple
In this silence, not bad
Ctrl a to select all and add sound effects
Click on the sound effects panel
You can favorite your own sound effects
Place it in the sound effects folder
Let's find a background sound
Select a sound effect
Press the spacebar to preview
Double-click this sound effect to insert it
If we select multiple lines
After insertion
It says 8R here
that is 8 lines
Look at the bottom right corner of this line, there's an identifier
represents the association of this row, this sound effect
Hold down the Ctrl key and scroll
If changed to 5
there are only 5 lines left
You can see that the sixth line does not have this identifier.
Let's change it to 8
Press the spacebar to preview sound effects and audio
The young hero kneels before the ancient temple Buddha
In this silent late night
The sound effect is a bit loud
The young hero knelt before the Buddha in the ancient temple
In this silent late night
he heard it from me, I hope
Sound effect appears first, then the cursor
Place it here
double-click pause
Press the Ctrl key to scroll
This pause is a stop
2 seconds
Finally, also pause for 1 second
If you don't add pauses
There will also be a pause of 0.3 seconds between these two lines
These two lines are spoken simultaneously
I can make them have a slight time offset
Xiao Zhang speaks first
Xiao Wang speaks later, these two lines are spoken in unison
Let's continue to listen to the sound effects
You can search in the sound effects panel, then expand all
Double-click it and it will be inserted here
Ahhh
Enter 'crow' to find a sound effect
Insert it here
Insert a sound effect
after a short segment of sound
Insert sound effect here
We'll insert a few sound effects
Double-click to add a pause
Hold down the Ctrl key and place the cursor at this location
Finally, add another pause
The person has already stopped speaking
but the sound gradually fades away
Regarding sound effects
I'll just briefly match these few
Ctrl a select all
select synthesis
Output completed, click on the output directory
These files with timestamps are the final audio outputs.
Several versions have been output in total
with sound effects only
Let's listen to the mixed version
The young hero knelt before the Buddha in the ancient temple
In this silent late night
He heard two voices from the depths of his soul
Give it up. Do you really think you can save the common people?
Turn back before it's too late
Put down your sword
You can live a peaceful and stable life
Isn't that what you've always wanted?
Don't listen to him
Pick up the sword
Just kill them all
All the power and wealth in this world will be yours.
Those are all illusions
Only power is eternal
Make your move and tell me what your choice really is
Now I'll switch to another project
Let's quickly explain batch rendering again.
Batch rendering can achieve the ultimate, detailed output.
Select the composition
It is only used for some debugging.
When you think the project is good
Save the project and use batch rendering
Let's briefly make this edit and save the project
By default, it will assign a name
You can also change it
Click Save
after that
Click Batch Render
if you have multiple projects
It can all be batch rendered.
Select it to open and start synthesis
Normally
If selected for synthesis
we can only output a combined audio effect
but during batch rendering
We can separate the sound effects
This is the background sound
This is the sound effect
Oops
If you think the sound effect is too loud
lower the volume
But this is not precise enough
For more precision, drag the sound effect in
Drag this sound effect 2 in
This sound effect can be preserved in segments
Look here
For example, if you don't want this sound, just delete it.
It is lossless
feel this sound is too loud
we'll just turn down the volume
Let's check the voice retention again
This old monk only said one sentence.
this Jiumozhi
said two sentences
Qiao Feng also said a few words
We overlay them together
The achieved effect is exactly the same as our overall mix.
This is the overall mix
We can place it at the back and compare it.
I'm dragging the subtitles in as well
Everyone, today we're not talking about the Muscle Change Classic
let's talk about the passive voice in English
In the martial world
Are you the one hitting or getting hit
This status must, the sound effect volume is a bit too loud, turn it down a little.
The status of getting beaten must be clearly understood
Amitabha
Patron Qiao is absolutely right
When I was in Tibet, I often felt that the passive voice was full of philosophy.
Well said, well said
The Discipline Hall teaches that those who make mistakes must be punished
Being punished is the most authentic passive
Then just prefer to use it directly, go for the ultimate move
eat the best that's
Qiao Feng took a deep breath
It is said that Qiao Feng is a hero.
This is a quick demonstration of AI voiceover.
We'll go into more detail in the next lesson
That's all for this lesson.